Tewogbade S. Fatai

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

About me

Front-End Web Developer with a passion for creating intuitive and engaging user experiences. Background in Architecture and earned a certificate in Front-End Website Development. Proven ability to excel in collaboration, creativity, and bringing projects from ideation to execution.

Website:

https://my-portfolio-2ecq.vercel.app/

Contact

Address:

Lagos State, Nigeria

Phone:

+234(0)8189733799

E-mail:

tewogbade3008@gmail.c om

Skills

HTML5

CSS

JavaScript

React JS

Git

NodeJS

Response Design

Bootstrap

Soft skills

Critical thinking,

Design development,

Time management,

Strong verbal and written communicator

Work History 08. 2022-**Web Development Intern** Tech Accent Creatives 12. 2022 Wrote well designed, testable, efficient code by using best software development Designed website layout/user interface by using standard HTML/CSS and JavaScript best practices Assist in integrating data from various backend services and databases using NodeJS and ExpressJS. Test and give feedback on new and existing technologies. Lead Architect 01.2021-Atrium Architecture and Designs Till date Created, printed and modified drawings in AutoCAD and Revit. Coordinated with segment leaders to promote architectural goals and design concepts. Consulted with clients to determine functional and spatial requirements of new structure. Calculated cost estimates for smaller to larger projects. Design Architect 10.2019-Luca Visage – Scavolini

12, 2020

- Successfully managed high-end kitchen showroom and also carried different phases of sales transactions. Assisted in creating a strong visual П appearance of the showroom by effective executing merchandise plans and strategies.
- Designed and executed more than 20n high-end kitchens for various clients
- Calculated cost estimates for smaller to larger projects.
- Organized and maintained blueprint files.

Languages

English

Interests

Working out Cooking Movies

Work History

09. 2018- 09. 2019	Junior Architect R+Y Projects, Lagos, Nigeria
	 Created, printed and modified drawings in AutoCAD and Revit. Coordinated with segment leaders to promote architectural goals and design concepts. Consulted with clients to determine functional and spatial requirements of new structure. Calculated cost estimates for smaller to larger projects.
01. 2013- 06. 2014	Architectural Intern Linesmith design associate
	 Created, printed and modified drawings in AutoCAD and Revit. Coordinated with segment leaders to promote architectural goals and design concepts. Consulted with clients to determine functional and spatial requirements of new structure. Calculated cost estimates for smaller to larger projects.

Education

01 . 2023-	Responsive Web Design Course Free Code Camp
2014- 2018	Bachelor of Architecture, BSc University of Ilorin, Ilorin.
2011- 2013	National Diploma Yaba College of Technology, Lagos.